<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Thorben Andresen</title>
 <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-03-10T14:06:11-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Thorben Andresen</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Week 11: A New Sense of Direction</title>
   <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-11"/>
   <updated>2015-03-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week11</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;!--Countdown until launch - &lt;span class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot;&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Countdown until launch on May 15th&lt;/b&gt; &lt;text id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot; class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;/text&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;../assets/js/countdown.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  var clock = document.getElementById(&quot;countdown-holder&quot;)
    , targetDate = new Date(2015, 04, 15); 
 
  clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  setInterval(function(){
    clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  }, 1000);
  /** http://countdownjs.org/readme.html
  https://blog.smalldo.gs/2013/12/create-simple-countdown**/
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to my blog!&lt;/em&gt; I write here about my journey as a first-time entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is kind of the moment of truth, because I have promised to to decide on one or more niches to focus on by March 6th. And so I did! All that research of the last two weeks enabled my to connect a lot of dots and helped me to craft a  clear vision. This revived sense of direction id very motivating and I cant wait to get my new ideas out there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Niches&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of focusing on a specific niche, I focus on a set of niches which are matching the following criteria:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are freelancers, aka. soloprenuers, aka. 1099ers (named after the IRS tax form which they use to report their earnings)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working mainly remotely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working mainly in front of a computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invoice often&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Require flexible billing options (one-time, recurring payments, etc.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are not regulated &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not use specialized billing standards (such as medical billing codes, etc) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on these criteria, I have decided to focus on what I would call &amp;quot;web-based (or browser-based) freelancers&amp;quot; which would be in the ballpark of two million Americans:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online Marketing Experts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Illustrators, Designers &amp;amp; other Creatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virtual Assistants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life &amp;amp; Business Coaches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent Consultants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know, having several niches is not exactly following the philosophy of the bootstrapping gurus over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefoundation.io&quot;&gt;The Foundation.io&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.softwarebyrob.com&quot;&gt;Rob Wallin&lt;/a&gt;. Sure, its not as easy to market to several niches at the same time as it would be with one niche. However I think that this group of niches is very homogeneous in terms of how they would use my app. And if this assumption turns out to be false, it is still possible to drop a niche without having wasted too much resources. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, there are many freelancer who offer services in more than one of these groups. I don&amp;#39;t want to loose leads by giving the impression that this product would only be beneficial for a certain niche. Its not! It could be even very beneficial for more niches then the ones I listed above. The main point I am making is that I am focusing on users with a certain common workflow and problem, not a common profession name. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have a re-established my hypothesis of the product-market fit, I need to move into validation stage. You can thank &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/The-Lean-Startup-Entrepreneurs-Continuous/dp/0307887898&quot;&gt;Eric Ries&lt;/a&gt; for making my last sentence sound so fancy. So by this week I want reach the following goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crafting a new version of my mockup&lt;/strong&gt; This will help the get the ideas in my head in concrete concepts and help me to communicate it with my potential clients, co-founders and/or developers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reach out to 20 new prospects&lt;/strong&gt; I expect to be tied up all week in the development of the new mockup, but I want to get the ball rolling anyways.  My goal is to get 5 pre-sales before I got into development. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, I better get to work now! Current excitement levels are high so I need to take advantage of that momentum. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please post them below. If
you liked this post, you can
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-11&amp;text=Week 11: A New Sense of Direction&amp;via=thorbenandresen&quot; 
   target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thorbenandresen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Week 10: Status & Using Virtual Assistants</title>
   <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-10"/>
   <updated>2015-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week10</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;!--Countdown until launch - &lt;span class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot;&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Countdown until launch on May 15th&lt;/b&gt; &lt;text id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot; class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;/text&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;../assets/js/countdown.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  var clock = document.getElementById(&quot;countdown-holder&quot;)
    , targetDate = new Date(2015, 04, 15); 
 
  clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  setInterval(function(){
    clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  }, 1000);
  /** http://countdownjs.org/readme.html
  https://blog.smalldo.gs/2013/12/create-simple-countdown**/
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to my blog!&lt;/em&gt; I write here about my journey as a first-time entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be a short post. As I have said last week, I committed myself to have a final decision on which niche(s) to target on by March 6st. I am now half-way through my research and have accomplished the tasks I set for myself last week, which were: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payment Processors Research&lt;/strong&gt; - I have now a pretty good idea of what&amp;#39;s out there, what&amp;#39;s possible and what&amp;#39;s not. Of course, more question will pop up along the way, but for now I feel comfortable with what I know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Niche Research&lt;/strong&gt; - The same is true for the niche research. I think I have a now a good understanding about the various kinds of soloprenuer niches and already an idea of what I am probably going to focus on. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the goals for week 10: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Research&lt;/strong&gt; - My VA has sent me this morning the initial list of the competitors in soloprenuer invoicing &amp;amp; billing space along with a couple of metrics I have asked for. I will now enrich this list with a couple of metrics myself. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole point is to make sure that my product has a unique selling preposition (USP). And the concept I have in mind is so far unique, which is something I am very excited about. Sure, there could be a good reason for it - e.g. it is not technically feasible or that it is simply not that beneficial for customers in the first place. But for right now, my glass is half full and I am confident that both of these explanations are wrong. And I guess there is only one way to figure this out anyways. (Especially if you are an advocate of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/The-Day-Startup-Learn-Launch-ebook/dp/B00NZFKB8S&quot;&gt;Dan Norris&amp;#39;s book &amp;quot;The 7-Day Startup&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;, which argues that you don&amp;#39;t learn until you launch.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Virtual Assistant&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a final note I want express how much I value having a Virtual Assistant (VA for my administrative, research &amp;amp; data entry tasks. Having one or more VAs can really leverage your startup and I recommend reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.asmartbear.com/virtual-assistant-startup.html&quot;&gt;this great article&lt;/a&gt;  by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.softwarebyrob.com&quot;&gt;Rob Wallin&lt;/a&gt; if you want to know more. My friend David Schneider from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.selfmadebusinessman.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Selfmade Businessman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has also written &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.selfmadebusinessman.com/2014/03/03/the-ultimate-guide-to-vas/&quot;&gt;an awesome step-by-step guide on how to hire VAs&lt;/a&gt; which shouldn&amp;#39;t leave any question open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please post them below. If
you liked this post, you can
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-10&amp;text=Week 10: Status &amp; Using Virtual Assistants&amp;via=thorbenandresen&quot; 
   target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thorbenandresen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Week 9: Research Paralysis?</title>
   <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-9"/>
   <updated>2015-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week9</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;!--Countdown until launch - &lt;span class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot;&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Countdown until launch on May 15th&lt;/b&gt; &lt;text id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot; class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;/text&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;../assets/js/countdown.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  var clock = document.getElementById(&quot;countdown-holder&quot;)
    , targetDate = new Date(2015, 04, 15); 
 
  clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  setInterval(function(){
    clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  }, 1000);
  /** http://countdownjs.org/readme.html
  https://blog.smalldo.gs/2013/12/create-simple-countdown**/
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to my blog!&lt;/em&gt; I write here about my journey as a first-time entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, here we go for the first review of my weekly commitments. I say it straight out, I did not complete the goals I set last week: I am still missing the decision on which niche(s) to focus on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? Well, first of all - as always - I underestimated the amount of work which goes into it. A good rule of thumb would be to take my initial best estimate and multiply it by two, and sometimes even three.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let&amp;#39;s dig a little deeper: If you want to hit the sweet spot, you need to align all three sides of the following triangle: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;User goals, business goals &amp;amp; technical goals.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/triangle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Thorben&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.slideshare.net/fling/designing-mobile-experiences-10013353&quot;&gt;Brian Fling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always thought I had a great good grip on user goals &amp;amp; business goals of Paybeat. However I totally underestimated the technical goals part of it. I still think it&amp;#39;s not a big challenge to build it, that&amp;#39;s not the issue here. The issue is the extend to which the technical goals influences the other two sides of the triangle. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Influence on Business Goals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an example, consider whether or not the payment processor allows me to customize something which is the known as the &amp;quot;soft descriptor&amp;quot;. Such a descriptor is basically the text which describes the transaction on your credit card or bank statement. If it&amp;#39;s unclear to the customers where this transaction is coming from, they might disputed it. This can be relatively costly - i.e. it has a significant influence on the business goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Influence on User Goals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example is whether you want to let the users create their own merchant accounts e.g. with &amp;quot;Stripe Connect&amp;quot;. Even though these accounts are free and take only 2 minutes to sign up for, they add considerably more friction to the user expierence. This is especially important when you build an app which competitive advantage largely lies in its simplicity and ease of use. And now imagine that you also might have to sign up for a separate merchant account in order to accept ACH payments. This example shows how the technical feasibility influences the user goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Competition&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But its not only the technical feasibility which requires more research, so does the competition. I was always sure that everyone of my competitors charges the same transaction fees and that these competitors use their feature set to differentiate themselves. This believe was destroyed when I came across a startup which charged considerably lower transaction fees than what every one else is doing. I can at the moment not explain how they can make this happen (especially when its a free app), other than that they are VC-backed and primarily aim to build a large user base. It would be a bad choice for a bootstrapper to compete with this startup. This competitor was not on my radar because it was hiding in niche. This means that I also need to spend more time doing competitive research. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Research Paralysis?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now don&amp;#39;t get me wrong - I am well aware of the term &amp;quot;research paralysis” and many argue that this is also only a fancier term for procrastination. You can of course never remove all uncertainty and this is also what makes entrepreneurship exciting. Therefore I have &lt;strong&gt;committed myself to have a final decision on which niche(s) to target on by March 6st!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the goals for week 9: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payment Processors Research&lt;/strong&gt; - Make a spreadsheet of the most popular payment processors on the market and collect all relevant details. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Niche Research&lt;/strong&gt; - Enhancing my spreadsheet of relevant niches with columns like &lt;em&gt;transaction frequency&lt;/em&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;em&gt;transaction volume&lt;/em&gt;. Furthermore I will research the invoicing &amp;amp; payment workflows as well as the regulations which govern these niches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The competitive research is due for next week. I have assigned my Virtual Assistant to create an initial list with a couple of easy-to-obtain details so that I dont have to start from scratch next week and can focus on the most important issues of the research. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please post them below. If
you liked this post, you can
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-9&amp;text=Week 9: Research Paralysis?&amp;via=thorbenandresen&quot; 
   target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thorbenandresen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My commitments for Week 8</title>
   <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-8"/>
   <updated>2015-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week8</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;!--Countdown until launch - &lt;span class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot;&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Countdown until launch on May 15th&lt;/b&gt; &lt;text id=&quot;countdown-holder&quot; class=&quot;post-date&quot;&gt;&lt;/text&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;../assets/js/countdown.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  var clock = document.getElementById(&quot;countdown-holder&quot;)
    , targetDate = new Date(2015, 04, 15); 
 
  clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  setInterval(function(){
    clock.innerHTML = countdown(targetDate, null, null,5).toString();
  }, 1000);
  /** http://countdownjs.org/readme.html
  https://blog.smalldo.gs/2013/12/create-simple-countdown**/
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to my blog!&lt;/em&gt; I want to write about my journey as a first-time entrepreneur. I haven&amp;#39;t really figured out yet what type of content I will post and how often I update the blog. However, I am sure that I will find my style and rhythm along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this first post I want to document my commitments I made for the coming &lt;em&gt;Week 8&lt;/em&gt;. My plan is to put out such a &lt;em&gt;commitment post&lt;/em&gt; once a week, and I hope that it will be interesting for you to read along. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will hold myself accountable to these goals and evaluate my progress by the end of the week. In that sense, writing about my progress will help me to stay focused. These goals have the highest priority, i.e. I will not do any other work before these goals are completed &lt;em&gt;(except for the scheduled phone calls with potential clients)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further ado, here is my goal for next week: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having decided on which niche or niches I want to focus on for my product &lt;em&gt;Paybeat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To break this down even further:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brainstorm an initial list of professions by:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google / Quora research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Government statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Making a list of competitors (via getapp.com) and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;... looking at the niches those competitors are targeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a list for criteria to select niches, such as:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being a solo-entreprenuer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 10.000 in niche&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High volume of invoices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;regulatory framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research the regulatory framework for each of these niches via:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google / Quora research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert interviews on Clarity.fm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate niches based on the criteria list and deciding on a niche or niches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to goal setting, the &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; is obviously more important than the &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt;. Therefore I will also always provide a short section about the reason for pursuing these stated goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have started to focus on the &lt;em&gt;Life &amp;amp; Business Coaches&lt;/em&gt; niche since the beginning of this year. I have so far talked to about ten coaches and experts on the phone and many more through social media. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have quickly learned that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A large percentage of the 55,000 coaches worldwide are only working part time, which means that they do not have very many clients to invoice. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many coaches considers their business a hobby/passion rather than a business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many coaches are low tech&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum it up, coaching is a unfortunately a terrible niche for creating (any kind of) specialized B2B SaaS software for. As a result, I need to either broaden or shift my focus to other niches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please post them below. If
you liked this post, you can
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Week-8&amp;text=My commitments for Week 8&amp;via=thorbenandresen&quot; 
   target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thorbenandresen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>First Post</title>
   <link href="http://www.thorbenandresen.com/first-post"/>
   <updated>2015-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thorbenandresen.com/Test2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to my blog!&lt;/em&gt; This is the first post and a only placeholder. This blog is made with &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;Poole template&lt;/a&gt;. Read more about it on &lt;a href=&quot;http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole/&quot;&gt;Joshua Lande&amp;#39;s Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or comments, please post them below. If
you liked this post, you can
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://www.thorbenandresen.com/first-post&amp;text=First Post&amp;via=thorbenandresen&quot; 
   target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  share it with your followers&lt;/a&gt; 
or 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thorbenandresen&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
  follow me on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
